# Iulian Prodea



iulian.prodea@outlook.com

linkedin.com/in/iulian-pro



+44 7424 693338



Willing to relocate across the UK



https://iulian.pro



https://github.com/iulianpro

# **Summary**

Recently graduated with an EQF Level 5 Diploma in Software Development at Code Institute Ireland, following the passion I have always had for technology and web development and which I wanted to raise it to a professional level after a fantastic career in Insurance, problem solving person, "Can Do" attitude, hardworking, 100% involved in professional activity.

I have always been noticed by the management of the companies where I worked. Each time I was promoted to senior positions and even to management positions.

I have been and I am very determined to become an experienced software developer, I continue to learn new things day by day and I am convinced that I will be able to bring add-value to the organization I will work for and I will be a winning investment for that company.

# **Experience**



## **Waking Night Support Care Worker**

Holmleigh Care Homes Ltd Aug 2019 - Aug 2020 (1 year 1 month)

As a waking night support care worker I was responsible with:

- Assisting Service Users with Personal Care and domestic duties.
- Create opportunities for Service Users to develop establish and maintain personal relationships and social networks, which encourage greater participation and integration in their chosen communities.
- Monitoring progress and recording notes on daily record sheets.

Recommendation: I'm happy to provide you contact details.



### **Area Sales Manager**

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Oct 2015 - Aug 2019 (3 years 11 months)

I have coordinated the activity of eight branches, meaning a team over 25 employees. Main responsibilities and actions has been:

- Driving sales processes and employees teams from eight territorial branches from NW of Romania;
- Developing strategies for growing business relationships with the company's partners;
- Recruitment candidates for vacancies;
- Tracking and fulfilling targets goals;
- Monitoring activity of the competition;

Achievements: Together with the sales teams, I managed to increase the company's client portfolio as well as sales volumes by 30% each year.

Recommendation: I'm happy to provide you contact details.



### Branch Manager

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Bucharest Romania

Oct 2013 - Sep 2015 (2 years)

In this position I was responsible for:

- Launching, developing and coordinating a new branch in Bucharest;
- Developing strategies for growing business relationships with the company's partners;
- Recruitment candidates for vacancies;
- Tracking and fulfilling targets goals;
- Monitoring activity of the competition;

Achievements: I was noticed by the company's management as one of the most productive employees, as proof that the Country Sales Manager proposed me to take over the position of Branch Manager.

Recommendation: I'm happy to provide you contact details.



#### Insurance Consultant

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Bucharest Romania

Apr 2012 - Sep 2013 (1 year 6 months)

In this position I was responsible for:

- Meeting with customers, understanding their needs and proposing tailored insurance solutions;
- Contacting existing customers by phone and proposing new insurance policies;
- Providing advices and support on insurance issues;
- Prospecting the market and identifying new potential customers;
- Identification of cross-selling solutions in order to increase the volume of sales;

Achievements: I was noticed by the company's management as one of the most productive employees, as proof that the Country Sales Manager proposed me to take over the position of Branch Manager.

Recommendation: I'm happy to provide you contact details.

# **Education**

# 0

# Code Institute Ireland

EQF Level 5 Diploma, Full Stack Software Developer 2019 - 2020

The course provided by the Code Institute was segmented into four chapters:

**User Centric Frontend Development:** 

- HTML Fundamentals;
- CSS Fundamentals;
- Bootstrap 4;
- GitHub;
- Git Version Control;
- VS Code:
- Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/my-city/

#### **Interactive Frontend Development:**

- · Javascript;
- jQuery;
- JSON;
- DOM Manipulation;
- Google Maps APIs;
- Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/discover-transylvania/

#### Data Centric Development:

- Databases Fundamentals;
- Python Fundamentals;
- SQL and noSQL;
- MySQL;
- Manipulated data with Python;
- Flask Framework;
- MongoDB;
- CRUD Operations;
- Project: https://iulianpro-shifts-manager.herokuapp.com/

## Full Stack Frameworks With Django:

- · Django Framework;
- Stripe;
- Amazon Web Services (S3);
- Project: https://iulianpro-give-help.herokuapp.com/